[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "By the end of the movie, Raiders of the Lost Ark, which character does not survive?", "correct_answer": "Belloq", "incorrect_answers": ["Sallas", "Marion", "Markus Brody"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the world of computers, what does PC stand for?", "correct_answer": "Personal Computer", "incorrect_answers": ["Private Computer", "Privileged Computing", "Programmable Computer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At what age does a wolf usually leave its pack?", "correct_answer": "2-3 years", "incorrect_answers": ["5-6 years", "1-2 years", "3-4 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was Rocky IV released?", "correct_answer": "1985", "incorrect_answers": ["1986", "1984", "1987"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the female saber-toothed squirrel that makes a debut appearance in Ice Age 3?", "correct_answer": "Scratte", "incorrect_answers": ["Sarah", "Debbie", "Scottie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why was Timothy in the Rack trap in Saw III?", "correct_answer": "He was responsible for the death of Jeffs son.", "incorrect_answers": ["He killed his wife.", "He was an escaped convict.", "He fled the scene of a crime."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these movies, starring Tom Hanks won the most Oscars?", "correct_answer": "Forrest Gump", "incorrect_answers": ["Saving Private Ryan", "Philadelphia", "Splash"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What  does the Latin word facula refer to?", "correct_answer": "Bright spots or patches on the suns photosphere", "incorrect_answers": ["A region of unexplained loss of gravity beneath the earths outer crust", "A measurement of the suns reflectivity", "A dark region on the suns chromosphere"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On November 3, 1896, a British company did this for the first time.", "correct_answer": "Issue an auto insurance policy", "incorrect_answers": ["Build an underground, electrically heated home", "Develop vulcanized rubber", "Set up the millionth telephone in Britain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did Tami call her orange car in the film Another Cinderella Story?", "correct_answer": "great pumpkin", "incorrect_answers": ["beautiful convertible", "old thing", "square orange"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "William Lioncheate is the name of the George W. Bush appointed Secretary of Housing and Urban Development.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of this US state means great river and its symbol is the magnolia tree.", "correct_answer": "Mississippi", "incorrect_answers": ["Missouri", "Massachusetts", "Minnesota"]}]